womanwithin.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy | Woman Within

The FULLBEAUTY Brands family of brands, which includes Woman Within®, Jessica London®, Roaman's®, SwimsuitsForAll®, FullBeauty®, Ellos®, KingSize®, BrylaneHome® and any other brands owned or operated by FULLBEAUTY Brands, Inc. or any of its affiliates from time to time (collectively, “FULLBEAUTY Brands”), understands that you care about how we collect, use, and share information when you interact with our websites, social media sites and handles, email and online services (our “Services”) and we value the trust you place in us. This Privacy Policy explains:

We also include specific disclosures for residents of California.

This Policy applies to all of the FULLBEAUTY Brands websites (collectively, the “FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites”), as well as social media sites and handles, your email address, emails we send, as well as the information we collect when you interact with us through other online services. It also applies anywhere it is linked. It does not apply to non-FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites and mobile applications that may link to the Services or be linked to or from the Services; please review the privacy policies on those websites and applications directly to understand their privacy practices. 

For questions about our privacy practices, contact us at:

FULLBEAUTY Brands, Inc.  
One New York Plaza  
New York, NY 10004  
Attn: General Counsel  
Email: PrivacyOfficer@fbbrands.com 

###  Information We Collect 

**Information you give us** : Some of the Services may include features or services that permit you to enter contact information and other information about you. We collect and store any information you enter on our Services. This includes: 

  * Contact and demographic information when registering to use our Services.
  * Payment information and associated contact information when engaging in a transaction on any FULLBEAUTY Brands Website. For international shipments, we may be required to collect special import identification numbers for customs purposes.
  * Email address information when subscribing to our emails.
  * Any information or data you provide by interacting in our chat, by submitting a product review, or by commenting on content posted on our Services.
  * Information you provide when you complete a survey administered by us or a service provider acting on our behalf.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence and any contact information provided. We record telephone conversations with our customer service center for record-keeping, training, and quality assurance purposes.

**Information We Collect From Others** : We may receive information about you from external parties in order to allow us to provide joint service offerings or inform you about products that we think you may be interested in. This includes: 

  * Contact information and information about your transaction if you purchase one of our products from a third-party seller.
  * Information about you, including mailing address or email address and other information about your potential interests and demographics, in order to send you catalogs, product offerings, or promotional offers. We may also send you branded private label credit card offers based on demographic information we receive. 
  * Contact information from someone you know who purchased a product for you or provided your information through a referral program. 

**Information We Collect Automatically** : When you interact with the Services, certain information about your use of our Services is automatically collected. Much of this information is collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies, as well as through your web browser or device. This includes: 

  * Details of your visits to any of our FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites and information generated in the course of the use our site (including the timing, frequency and pattern of service use) including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, the resources that you access, and how you reached our site.
  * Details regarding the device you use to access our Services, including, but not limited to, your IP address, operating system and browser type.
  * Information about how you interact with our ads and newsletters, including whether you open or click links in any correspondence.
  * Information that you make available to us on a social media platform (such as by clicking on a social media icon linked from our Services), including your account ID or username and other information included in your posts.

### How We Use and Protect Your Information

We may use the information we collect from you for the following purposes:

  * To provide you with our products and services, including to take steps to transact a sale or for services, process payments, fulfill orders, and send service communications.
  * To enable additional features on our Services and to provide you with a personalized service.
  * To notify you regarding products, services, and promotions that may be if interest to you. 
  * To create custom audiences on social media sites.
  * To provide you with the best service and improve and grow our business, including understanding our customer base and purchasing trends, and understanding the effectiveness of our marketing, and tailoring advertising to you.
  * To detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be fraudulent or illegal, and to comply with legal requirements regarding the provision of products and services.

**How We Secure the Information We Collect From or About You**

We use a combination of physical, technical, and administrative safeguards to protect the information we collect through the Services. While we use these precautions to safeguard your information, we cannot guarantee the security of the networks, systems, servers, devices, and databases we operate or that are operated on our behalf.

### Our Sharing of Your Information

  * **Service Providers** : We engage vendors to perform functions on our behalf such as: website, software, and data storage, content management, customer communications, database management, technical integration, marketing automation, analytics, website optimization, conducting customer surveys, shipping, and payment processing.

There are limited circumstances in which the service provider collects data directly from you when their privacy policies may also apply.

  * **Social Media Platforms** : Where you choose to interact with us through social media, your interaction with these programs typically allows the third party to collect some information about you through digital cookies they place on your device and other tracking mechanisms. In some cases, the third party may recognize you through its digital cookies even when you do not interact with their application. Please visit the third parties’ respective privacy policies to better understand their data collection practices and controls they make available to you.
  * **Branded Private Label Credit Card Accounts** : If you hold a branded private label credit card, we share information with the bank that issues branded private label credit card accounts, Comenity Bank. Shared information includes the date of the order, the type of payment, the amount of the order, and similar items, and may also include your name, address or other contact information. To obtain a privacy policy, opt-out information, or contact information, for any of the branded private label credit card programs, you may contact the Bank by clicking through to the following link: <https://comenity.com/>.
  * **Third parties involved in advertising** : We partner with third parties who assist us in serving advertising regarding the Services to others who may be interested in the Services. We also partner with third parties who use cookies to display interest-based advertising to you on the Services. These third parties may use tracking technologies on our FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites to collect or receive information from the Services and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. These third parties may allow other companies to access information about you so that they may market other products you may be interested in. Many digital advertising companies post their privacy practices online and may offer you options to control your information. 
  * **Corporate Affiliates** : Our FULLBEAUTY Brands family shares data with members of our group of companies and brands.
  * **Similar Companies** : We may share your mailing address directly with other companies who may sell services of interest to you. These companies are limited to using the address once for a mailing. 

### Additional Information About our Data Collection and Sharing Practices

**Information Relating to Children** : We believe it is important to safeguard the privacy of children and encourage parents to regularly monitor their children’s use of online activities. You must be age 18 or older to use this website or any of our services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18 years old. If you are a parent and believe that your child under the age of 18 has accessed and/or used our website or services or otherwise provided personal information to us, please contact us at or the mailing address at the end of this Privacy Policy and we will work to delete that account and any such personal information. 

**Legal Disclosures** : If we are required to disclose customer information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, in response to law enforcement inquiry or in compliance with applicable laws, we will make such disclosure. We also may share information with legal authorities and other companies for purposes of fraud protection. 

**Sharing of Aggregated Data** : We may analyze aggregated, de-identified data and share these analyses at our discretion, including with marketing agencies, media agencies and analytics providers. These third parties will not be able to relate this data to identifiable individuals. 

**Combination of Information** : We may combine information from the Services together and with other information we obtain from our business records. Additionally, information collected about you from a particular browser or device may be linked to information collected from another computer or device that we believe relates to you. 

**Personal Data Collected From You About Others** : If you decide to refer a friend to us, we will collect your and the third party’s names, e-mail addresses, street addresses, and/or phone numbers in order to send an e-mail or catalog and use this information to communicate with both you and your friend. You hereby agree that you will obtain the third party’s consent to this before giving us their personal data. You hereby agree not to send us the contact details of any legal minor. We will inform any friend you invite that he/she was referred by you in the invitation e-mail. 

**Change of Ownership or Corporate Organization** : We may transfer to another entity or its affiliates or service providers some or all information about you in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, acquisition, sale of assets or any line of business, change in ownership control, or financing transaction. We cannot promise that an acquiring party or the merged entity will have the same privacy practices or treat your information the same as described in this Policy. 

**Cross-border Transfer of Data** : If you use our Services outside of the United States, you understand that we may collect, process, and store your personal information in the United States and other countries. The laws in the U.S. regarding personal information may be different from the laws of your state or country. Any such transfers will comply with safeguards as required by relevant law. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, international transfer, storage, and processing of your data. 

### Your Options and Rights

Please visit the [My Account](https://www.womanwithin.com/my-account) page to update your contact information and payment method.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email bulletin or email us at [Unsubscribe@fbbrands.com](mailto:Unsubscribe@fbbrands.com) and we will promptly remove you from all correspondence.

If you would like to be removed from a paper catalog mailing list, you can email us by going to the relevant FULLBEAUTY Brands Website listed on the table below and clicking on the email link in the "Contact Us" section. Please make sure to provide us with your exact name and address as it appears on the mailing label from your catalog so that we can identify you correctly.

### Woman Within

Phone: | 1-800-248-2000  
---|---  
Address: | 500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912  
Website: | https://www.womanwithin.com/  
  
### Brylane Home

Phone: | 1-800-528-5150  
---|---  
Address: | 500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912  
Website: | https://www.brylanehome.com/  
  
### Ellos

Phone: | 1-800-405-3650  
---|---  
Address: | 500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912  
Website: | https://www.ellos.us/  
  
### Roaman's

Phone: | 1-800-436-0800  
---|---  
Address: | 500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912  
Website: | https://www.roamans.com/  
  
### King Size

Phone: | 1-800-846-1600  
---|---  
Address: | 500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912  
Website: | https://www.kingsize.com/  
  
### Jessica London

Phone: | 1-800-784-1667  
---|---  
Address: | 500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912  
Website: | https://www.jessicalondon.com/  
  
### fullbeauty

Phone: | 1-800-400-4481  
---|---  
Address: | 500 S. Mesa Hills Dr. El Paso, TX 79912  
Website: | https://www.fullbeauty.com/  
  
We will make every effort to implement any choice you make as soon as possible, but you should allow up to three months for mailing change requests to be fully implemented. Any mailings that you may receive during this time do not reflect your subscription status, and we ask that you please disregard them.

### Your California Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California have the right to request information regarding third parties to whom the company has disclosed certain categories of personal information during the preceding year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please email [PrivacyOfficer@fbbrands.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@FBBrands.com), write to us at FULLBEAUTY Brands, Inc., One New York Plaza, New York, NY 10004, Attn: General Counsel or call us at 1-800-781-9168. 

### Special Information For Nevada Residents

Residents of the State of Nevada have the right to opt out of the sale of certain pieces of their information to third parties who will sell or license their information to others. If you are a Nevada resident and would like to make such a request, please email [PrivacyOfficer@fbbrands.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@FBBrands.com).

### Changes to This Policy

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will post any changes, and such changes will become effective when they are posted. Your continued use of our Services following the posting of any changes will mean you accept those changes.

### Additional Information About Our Use of Tracking Technologies and Interest-Based Advertising

FULLBEAUTY Brands relies on partners to provide many features of our FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites and services using data about your use of the FULLBEAUTY Brands and other sites. We use cookies for the following purposes:

  * **Website Operations** : Enabling features that are necessary for providing you the services on our FULLBEAUTY Brands Websites, such as identifying you as being signed in, tracking content views, remembering your preferences and the number of times you have been shown an advertisement.
  * **Analytics** : Allowing us to understand how our services are being used, track website performance and make improvements.
  * **Personalized Advertising** : Delivering tailored advertising based on your preferences or interests across services and devices and measuring the effectiveness of ads.
  * **Social Media** : Enabling the sharing of content from our services through social networking and other websites.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to disable or reject cookies. If you delete your cookies or if you set your browser to decline cookies, some features of the Services may not be available, work, or work as designed. You may also be able to opt out of or block tracking by interacting directly with the third-parties who conduct tracking through our Services.

You can learn more about ad serving companies and the options available to limit their collection and use of your information by visiting the websites for the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1), the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN), and the [European Interactive Digital Advertising Initiative](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Similarly, you can learn about your options to opt-out of mobile app tracking by certain advertising networks through your device settings and by resetting the advertiser ID on your Apple or Android device. 

Please note that opting-out of advertising networks services does not mean that you will not receive advertising while using our Services or on other websites, nor will it prevent the receipt of interest-based advertising from third parties that do not participate in these programs. It will, however, exclude you from interest-based advertising conducted through participating networks, as provided by their policies and choice mechanisms. If you delete your cookies, you may also delete your opt-out preferences.

Your browser or device may include "Do Not Track" functionality. At this time, FULLBEAUTY Brands does not respond to browser "Do Not Track" signals.
